Send a message
Hello Hello friends welcome back to my channel
today we are going to talk about Digach Insurance
company it is a general insurance
company and for one it is a private general
insurance company I am talking about
ICICI General Insurance Salumber it is one of the
leading companies in the
mutual fund or choice stock if you are
adding it to your portfolio then it will
give you a lot of money so
add it to your portfolio for the long term it can help you in making a big profit I will
talk about this general
insurance company yesterday it was almost fixed it was
showing a rise of 3.7 cents
it is on the upside and its close was around
thirteen hundred rupees this
closing you can see its previous close is being
seen at 1254 rupees it opened at
1255 paper the high it
made was 1334 rupees whereas
in this it made 1253 rupees it
is a leading insurance company this is the
working of ICICI Lombard General Insurance
this company let's see it  In the past few
years,
how it has given returns to its investors,
you can see that in one day it
is 3.68 percent, the return it has given in a week is
5.05 percent,
in one month the return that ICICI Lombard has given to
its investors is
5.5 percent, whereas
in 2020 ICICI Lombard has given a return of about 60 percent
in one year, the return it has given is
about 14.72 percent,
it has not given any return in 3 years
because you know there is no
listing of such old shares, no data of 3 years file or 10 years
is available, so of which
player, that is why it is an old listing, otherwise
let us see
how the trading happened on NSC in it last day, the closing
price was seen to be
around 13 percent, if you look at the volume straight in it, then on
that day it was 31 lakh 96 thousand
259 towards face value juice
You can see that ₹10 is whose low is 52,
that is 800 ₹5, 52 also eat its range is
14 to ₹40, it is a big company, it
can make you a millionaire, if you are
adding it to your portfolio for the long term,
by long term I mean at least for 15 to
20 years, if you
add it to your portfolio then it is going to give you
huge returns, now
you can see the return given by Stark in one year, it has given a return of 14.72 percent, it is a
company blocking the insurance sector,
market capital of 58758 crores, it is one of the large cap companies,
so you must add it to your portfolio
so that you can get multiplication
returns, that is, it
can give you returns with less problem effect, it is a great company,
let us see the system quarterly results
which have just come in March,
so what we are going to compare is the
result of December 19th and March 20th, so
from the net, the December  It was 90, it
was 56 crores in 2004, which has now become
2345, due to the fall in oil, a
fall of about four and a half percent will be
seen in sales, whereas its
operating profit which was 300, well,
due to this incident, the
fall in operating profit will be seen, a
fall of about 22.91 percent is being
seen in operating profit, let us
see the net profit of IS, the
net profit which was 90, was 294 and
in March it became 281, the
fall in operating profit is being
seen of about 4.14 percent,
operating profit margin has become
12.09 from 14.99, there is a fall
of about 2.9 percent in operating profit margin here, it is a
big company,
you know that the market is
going through a very bad situation due to Corona, hence, a
little correction has been seen in its results,
but a big company  It is
for the long term, you
must add it to your portfolio. The
holding share with the promoters
is 55.86 and 23.30 is available in it, that is the share
of the mutual fund,
that is 10.47 percent,
in non-institutional investor service, 7.75
is available at 57 percent, if you now have a
holding of 2.7 percent in it, then
big giants have invested in it, so
if you want to add it to your portfolio, then
adopt the buy on dips strategy, whenever there is a slight correction,
add it to your portfolio and
never invest a lump sum amount at once, you take the shares in S8 free mode, the
maturity shareholder
is the promoter in it and there is
no problem in the pledged shares, that is,
in 29 schemes of mutual fund, a
stay of 10.47 percent has been taken in it, it should be noted that 553
companies have taken a stay of 20.39 percent  The
promoter with the highest building is
ICICI Bank, which has a holding of 55.81 percent. The
IS public shareholder,
Question Fund, has a 2.1 percent stake. The
individual investor's holding is
5.6 percent, meaning
retail investors like us also
hold more than five and a half percent. So, this is a great company.
You can add it to your portfolio for the long
term. It will give you
multibagger returns. So, you must add it to your portfolio. You
can see the speed of ICICI Lombard. It is running at 49.5 percent. So, right now
it is cheaper than all these companies like HDFC SBI Live
and
you can see it cheaper than A Pool. So, you
can check its valuation. Its
valuation is the lowest even among its peer group companies. So,
you
must add it to your portfolio. If you
want to become a millionaire in 10-15 years from the market, then
ICICI General Insurance is the best.  There must be a certain amount of money
in your portfolio
so that you can earn money.